http://www.amusedmoose.com/mailing-list-privacy-policy/

Tweet
Your privacy is important.  We will only use the information that we collect about you in a fair and lawful way in accordance with GDPR 2018.
We will use your personal information to send email alerts in order to keep you up-to-date about shows, events, courses, awards and offers etc that we believe will be of interest to you, after you sign up to our mailing list at a comedy show, or by entering our award competitions, or request information about our comedy courses or about comedy generally.  Also the name and email address of people who work in the comedy industry may be added to our TalentScout dataset in order that we can invite them to attend showcases and events, and about comedy related matters.
We may also use the information for internal administration and analysis.  We promise to never sell, rent, trade or pass on your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes.
We will always give you the chance to Opt Out should you choose to do so.  At the bottom of every emailing generated by our group emailing system, that contains information about shows, events, courses and awards etc, there is an Opt Out option.  If you Opt Out we will stop sending you emailings, and we will delete your record completely if you email asking us to. �
The type of information we will collect about you includes:
Your name
Email address
Phone number if you have provided it
Address if you have added this yourself to your record in our database
Date of birth if you have added this yourself to your record in our database
Business role of those working in the comedy industry
We do NOT hold credit/debit card details because we sell tickets through reputable ticketing agencies.  They advise all their clients about their privacy policies.
Any personal information we hold will be held securely and in accordance with our internal security policy and the law.
We may use technology to track click-through links in emails sent as part of our e-bulletin subscription service.
By disclosing your personal information to us, either by using this website, by email, in person, or over the telephone, you consent to the collection, storage and processing of your personal information by Amused Moose Comedy and Comedy Training Courses (previously Stand Up And Deliver) in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy.
If you have any questions/comments about privacy, please do not hesitate to get in touch by sending an email to us: comedy@amusedmoose.com
�
< Back to previous page
Back to top
What's OnLocationsSubscribeComedy CoursesAmused Moose Comedy Awards
Edinburgh FringePerformersAbout UsOffersHighlightsPress & MediaProductionPast showsPrivacy PolicySearchSubsSitemapMailing List Privacy PolicyTwitterYoutubeInstagramFacebook
Amused Moose Comedy
Suite 1, Townsend House
22-25 Dean Street
Soho
London
W1D 3RY
UK
Office Phone Number:
020 7287 3727 / 07970 524 234
Contact:
comedy@amusedmoose.com
